<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-09-24T23:22:21.235Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:22:21.236Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile Empire]]></title>
        <id>Mobile Empire-1758755962690</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/mobile-empire/id1380582804?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:19:22.690Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺129,99 → ₺99,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/mobile-empire/id1380582804?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/35/fd/4f/35fd4fcb-381b-1ee8-d703-e4173dfb9613/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-0-0-9-0-0-sRGB-0-0-0-GLES2_U002c0-512MB-85-220-0-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺129,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺99,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Game Introduction
Mobile Empire is a simulation game based on "manufacturing mobile phones", with a high degree of freedom. You will play as an entrepreneur back in 2001. You acquired the initial capital from a mystery investor because of your unique vision and created a technological enterprise that may change the world. The game starts from 2001 and ends in 2035, during which you will start with old school smartphones in the early R&D stages, progressing until AR smart glasses can be independently used. During the 35 years, you will experience, witness, and promote the magnificent development process of smartphones. You have the chance to develop your company into the world's number one technological enterprise.

• Unique theme
Currently, Mobile Empire is probably the only PC simulation game based on "manufacturing mobile phones". You will have the chance to create miracles and develop your little-known company into a global technological empire. 

• Innovative competition experience
In order to simulate a real business environment, lots of competitors will be constantly updated. Players may cooperate with them for joint development or poach talents from them. 

• Massive amounts of random events
In order to create a better "sense of the world", a great deal of industrial events, world events, crisis events, lucky events, employee events, and news interviews are set in this game for you to make your own choices.

• Bountiful blueprints
The game includes 65 different cell phone blueprints and more than 100 cell phone appearances from 3x3 keypads to full-screen and folding screens, and even includes futuristic AR smart glasses. Bountiful blueprints are yours to explore. 

• Vast technologies
In this game, there are many technologies and accessories are available for upgrade. In addition, with adequate funds, you can even research and develop CPUs with superior performance and experience better operating systems. Customized naming is also supported.

• Creative persuasion system
In terms of talent recruitment, the game provides a very distinctive "persuasion" system. To acquire the top talents, you need to use different communication skills to persuade the recruits according to their personalities.

• Other contents for you to explore
The game also includes credit ratings, company acquisitions, employee development, outsourcing mode, intelligence system, company strategies, and more for you to explore.

• "Mobile Empire" IOS supports the archive of PC games.

Languages Supported:
*English
*简体中文 (Simplified Chinese)
*繁体中文 (Traditional Chinese)

Operating system 
iOS: version 8.0 or higher 

Recommended configuration 
RAM: 1 GB or more 
Storage: 1.5 GB 

Service Email：indie@xindong.com
©2020 X.D. Network Inc. All rights reserved.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/b8/fe/fc/b8fefc8b-6c32-b894-08e5-41f7b3fa2f00/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/d6/7e/cd/d67ecdae-7c6e-194a-686b-372215a3d749/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/f4/dd/2d/f4dd2d01-b058-0dec-5055-d39b6cb298f9/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/26/ed/8a/26ed8a89-a896-ab7d-4274-b9330df234b5/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/24/ce/1a/24ce1a52-ef89-0a2e-63b3-b03f807a27b4/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/7d/52/ff/7d52ff54-ba37-e55d-735e-ebb5ce3daf73/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/66/34/26/66342640-7d7c-8777-faca-aed8a6b7bad3/pr_source.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/0b/c6/c2/0bc6c265-10bd-42ba-4ede-8db2d1f2a806/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/31/65/7b/31657b19-4313-83e6-1afd-6d2c32144225/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/8c/d4/da/8cd4daa6-8f24-d4a1-a68f-55e66f940ba1/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/a1/22/f0/a122f04f-71a1-5a4b-32a7-4bf2505b19f1/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/b9/92/87/b99287bb-851f-588e-8ef3-00836061a3b3/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/56/5e/ea/565eea63-b50f-f5a2-9b28-c170058a67bf/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/f9/7c/64/f97c6426-a8f0-6428-ee44-c6d5a84103d0/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kingdom Rush Frontiers TD]]></title>
        <id>Kingdom Rush Frontiers TD-1758755962690</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/kingdom-rush-frontiers-td/id598581396?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:19:22.690Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺99,99 → ₺39,99<br/>Bonehart: ₺299,99 → ₺229,99<br/>Ashbite: ₺299,99 → ₺229,99<br/>Kutsao: ₺129,99 → ₺39,99<br/>Dante: ₺229,99 → ₺129,99<br/>Sha'tra: ₺129,99 → ₺39,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/kingdom-rush-frontiers-td/id598581396?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/ec/04/70/ec0470a6-3e3b-9fba-453e-30a34ddc6b81/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-5-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺99,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺39,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Bonehart：</strong><span>₺299,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺229,99</strong>
</b>
  </li><li>
    <strong>Ashbite：</strong><span>₺299,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺229,99</strong>
</b>
  </li><li>
    <strong>Kutsao：</strong><span>₺129,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺39,99</strong>
</b>
  </li><li>
    <strong>Dante：</strong><span>₺229,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺129,99</strong>
</b>
  </li><li>
    <strong>Sha'tra：</strong><span>₺129,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺39,99</strong>
</b>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Kingdom Rush Frontiers is a whole new level of the furiously fast, enchantingly charming gameplay that made kingdom Rush an award-winning Tower Defense hit.
Defend exotic lands from dragons, man-eating plants, and ghastly denizens of the underworld -all with flashy towers, levels, heroes, and more goodies to help you crush your enemies to a pulp.

BUILD MIGHTY TOWERS!
• OVER 18 TOWER ABILITIES! Unleash Death Riders, pestilence clouds, or assassins that steal and kill your enemies!
• 8 SPECIALIZED TOWER UPGRADES! Slice, sizzle, and stomp your foes with Crossbow Forts, Mighty Templars, Necromancers, and even Earthquake Machines - hey, we told you we were shaking things up.
• UPGRADE SYSTEM allows you to min/max your towers towards your preferred strategy.
• Fortify the frontier in exotic new lands - hold the line in deserts, jungles, and even the underworld!

TRAIN LEGENDARY HEROES
• 16 LEGENDARY HEROES. Choose among mighty champions and train their abilities! Each has unique specialties that fit different play styles and strategies!
• Special units and features on every stage! Watch out for the Black Dragon!

DEFEAT THEM ALL
• OVER 40 ENEMIES with unique abilities! Stay on your toes as you fight through desert sandworms, tribal shamans, nomad tribes, and underground terrors. Action like you have never seen before!
• MERCILESS BOSS FIGHTS! Hey, we told you to get those upgrades...

MORE MIND-BOGGLING CONTENT
• Hours of gameplay with OVER 80 ACHIEVEMENTS! what can you expect from Ironhide Games, the creators of Kingdom rush? You will be hooked for hours searching for Easter eggs and achievements!
• IN-GAME ENCYCLOPEDIA! learn all about your enemies and you will be able to plan the best strategy to defeat them. Study up!
• CLASSIC, IRON, AND HEROIC GAME MODES to challenge your tactical skills!
• 3 DIFFICULTY MODES! Are you up for a real challenge? Go with Hard mode!
• PLAY IT OFFLINE! No internet? No problem! You will be able to jump into real action even offline!

-----------------------------------------------------

PRAISE FOR KINGDOM RUSH: IGN Editor's Choice, Slide To Play Must Have, 148 Apps Editor's Choice, Jay is Games Game of the Year, Pocket Gamer Gold Award, Touch Arcade 4.5/5

Terms and Conditions:
https://www.ironhidegames.com/TermsOfService

Privacy Policy:
https://www.ironhidegames.com/PrivacyPolicy

Video creators, podcast creators, and streamers:
We would love to see your content on Youtube and Twitch! We support and promote channel creators so, if you want us to showcase your videos or want to know more about our games, feel free to write to us to contact@ironhidegames.com
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/78/8e/b0/788eb0fc-afa8-245b-799b-a195718790a4/5a6affe9-dc30-420d-a725-ad6aa8e9001b_screenshots_2208x12420001.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/79/98/cd/7998cd5a-99b1-b03b-4c9d-42f9c371611c/10e242a9-64da-43ec-a049-230d6672b48f_screenshots_2208x12420002.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/a0/87/32/a0873242-dd94-fe5d-70f4-ccc55b6d4d54/c1460a05-6fe6-422b-a563-4e245dd8af37_screenshots_2208x12420003.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple112/v4/9a/ba/96/9aba96b9-f838-936d-0524-c1f932ea79b3/7c12dd14-89b7-41c3-968b-33b7225a8730_screenshots_2208x12420004.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/a3/e1/00/a3e1007a-194c-5dc2-1c97-3c2991b1ab9c/436d4067-8ab6-4f41-9103-69ee4cd85a91_screenshots_2208x12420005.png/406x228bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juicy Realm]]></title>
        <id>Juicy Realm-1758755962690</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/juicy-realm/id1453808408?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:19:22.690Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺129,99 → ₺99,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/juicy-realm/id1453808408?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/0c/23/e7/0c23e71d-9853-40d0-4273-f6c08cb1369b/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺129,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺99,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Juicy Realm is a roguelike game with fruits as enemies. It is set in a world in which the line between animals and plants is blurred. It began with the tipping of the food-chain, which forced the humans to establish an outpost and begin an investigation in the region where the first species of mutated plants was discovered. The military has prepared a vast number of powerful weapons, with you leading the vanguard forces to wage this long war.

Subverted Order
“Many years later, when the humans watch as the plants climb up to the top of the food chain, they will be reminded of their own naivety and arrogance…”
Only when all the plants started to evolve into animals, growing limbs and becoming sentient, did the humans realize the threat of those photosynthetic-lifeforms. No one knows how they achieved the state of evolution that took animal lifeforms millions of years to reach in such a short amount of time, and no one knows their ultimate objective. The only thing known for sure is that the humans now face the greatest challenge since they climbed up to the top of the food chain.

Gameplay
As the first explorers of this unknown region, you must strive to venture deep into the enemy hive, defeat all kinds of fruits and arm yourself with various equipment, as well as upgrade yourself with the resources you find in your way.

Game Features
-Rougelite elements such as random terrains, loot drops, and monsters
-Hundreds of special and bizarre weapons and items
-Loads of unique mod enemies and bosses
-10 characters in the roster with unique skills and abilities
-Unique artstyle with rich details

Twitter: /@JuicyRealm
Facebook: @JuicyRealm
Press contact: juicyrealm@spacecangames.com

[Minimum Requirements]

Please make sure you are using devices matching the following requirements. If you are using old devices, the game might not run normally on your device.

iPhone 6S and higher
iPad Air 2 and higher
iPad Mini 4 and higher
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/3a/45/0a/3a450a53-b535-96da-505b-e15d4ee981ae/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/f0/c7/15/f0c7157f-7618-abcf-d022-22cab0453c31/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/e1/3b/ad/e13badd6-1686-70e6-e2c6-94976ed10288/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/95/0c/9c/950c9ca5-39fe-c66a-a9b4-fcdc5a14565c/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/c7/58/78/c758787b-6f28-cb09-1600-b63d4502f75d/pr_source.png/406x228bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/25/2a/62/252a62fe-c11d-7cbc-1c3a-4ea6531dca1e/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/84/8a/e0/848ae0ea-d8e0-8f67-4bfc-e1679ee028e4/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/6f/0a/e6/6f0ae677-31d6-1e47-f50c-8c956f30ae84/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/08/31/c8/0831c840-1232-6894-2310-e04ced38cef0/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/48/db/83/48db831b-ff2a-4d3a-f3bc-a3336e5070f6/pr_source.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vostok — Story Maker]]></title>
        <id>Vostok — Story Maker-1758755962690</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/vostok-story-maker/id1453318714?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:19:22.690Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺179,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/vostok-story-maker/id1453318714?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/40/f3/02/40f3029d-b0ec-557e-565c-2f86798e8baf/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-1-0-85-220.jpeg/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺179,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Welcome to Vostok – your ultimate companion for crafting captivating stories and stunning collages, designed to elevate your social media presence! With Vostok, transforming your ideas into professional-grade posts and stories is now a breeze.

Whether you're a blogger, photographer, or simply love sharing your life's moments on social media, Vostok provides all the tools you need to create content that will make an impact. Our sleek and user-friendly app seamlessly combines your passion for photography and storytelling, offering a dynamic platform to showcase your awe-inspiring moments.

Embracing a minimalist style, Vostok becomes your canvas for unlimited creativity. A vast collection of templates, stickers, and effects empowers you to design unique stories that reflect your individuality.

But Vostok goes beyond creative freedom; it's all about simplicity. Our intuitive interface makes editing and sharing your content effortless, freeing up more time for you to focus on crafting compelling narratives that your followers will adore.

No more waiting! Embark on your Vostok journey today and craft captivating posts and stories that leave a lasting impression!

Here's a glimpse of some of our features:

· 200+ design templates for social media
· Exclusive fonts with Cyrillic support
· 450+ unique stickers
· Atmospheric dust and grain effects for photos
· Variety of backgrounds: paper textures, marble, gradients, colors
· Ad-free with no subscription requirements
· Dark mode compatibility

Recognized as one of the Best Apps of 2019 by Apple.

With over 200+ templates, Vostok is your go-to toolkit for creating standout social media content.

We eagerly look forward to your ideas and feedback.
Connect with us at hello@vostokapp.ru or drop us a direct message on Instagram at @vostokapp.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/b3/6e/82/b36e82ad-6b1a-634a-e8e9-7a2cf4d393b3/1f4ac972-a5de-437f-a2be-6c52e212e58b_iPhone_8_Plus_-_1.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/e7/79/43/e77943f5-7b2c-c0d9-c0e2-622f24346dca/2c3e986b-2570-474e-bc2c-e0ac1149c384_iPhone_8_Plus_-_6.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/15/62/46/156246a6-3d3c-13bb-48be-5abd58af2e0e/291dcbb6-6a8a-4d03-8416-757be247c908_iPhone_8_Plus_-_3.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/50/53/32/5053322b-63da-bfc4-20e7-96b0e6199fb6/ce765125-a585-4f73-875d-8a968da54b31_iPhone_8_Plus_-_8.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/da/08/ad/da08add3-6e9c-26e8-4148-6732cdc92e07/4baa24af-fe38-4e48-8f06-7472bc3d5d37_iPhone_8_Plus_-_7.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/23/7d/b9/237db903-4b25-726d-1f0f-73487d1518a9/30e1bb0b-b1b4-4a09-8131-026b784e3b0e_iPhone_8_Plus_-_5.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/59/17/b0/5917b079-4128-d9c1-ba79-f11b7ea9bf1a/c266d2b9-a6a1-4ce9-9beb-f93a9234dca5_iPhone_8_Plus_-_4.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/43/95/a6/4395a691-d2f1-9c1a-7639-805526308049/d2690f31-81fe-4660-b18a-b899367b0330_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/f9/68/4b/f9684bd2-cf5e-e840-0851-77b807cf2b38/tns.fyzlgkiy.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/13/d1/a4/13d1a4d6-dfef-a0f3-f27a-387a16db8d9f/tns.ertgkjsq.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/3f/96/7d/3f967dbc-dfd1-d6c0-be5f-8ea65d8c562a/tns.grzffkss.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/5a/34/a7/5a34a7bf-ea0f-94cf-5e97-57c98e0ecef3/tns.imleqekv.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/17/0a/70/170a70f9-ac72-41c4-7c6e-efe2aff54be6/tns.tawfhfab.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[To the Moon]]></title>
        <id>To the Moon-1758755962690</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/to-the-moon/id1159700098?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:19:22.690Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺229,99 → ₺99,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/to-the-moon/id1159700098?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/b4/70/9a/b4709aac-55d1-21e8-89d4-ccdeccf04a1f/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺229,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺99,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  A story-driven experience about two doctors traversing backwards through a dying man's memories to artificially fulfill his last wish.

ABOUT THIS GAME
Dr. Rosalene and Dr. Watts have peculiar jobs: They give people another chance to live, all the way from the very beginning... but only in their patients' heads.

Due to the severity of the operation, the new life becomes the last thing the patients remember before drawing their last breath. Thus, the operation is only done to people on their deathbeds, to fulfill what they wish they had done with their lives, but didn’t.

This particular story follows their attempt to fulfill the dream of an elderly man, Johnny. With each step back in time, a new fragment of Johnny's past is revealed. As the two doctors piece together the puzzled events that spanned a life time, they seek to find out just why the frail old man chose his dying wish to be what it is.

And Johnny's last wish is, of course... to go to the moon.

MORE DETAILS
"To the Moon", a story-driven RPG with pixel graphics, was originally developed six years ago for PC by Canadian producer Kan Gao and Freebird Games, his indie game studio.Rights to develop and publish the remastered mobile version of "To the Moon" were acquired by X.D. Network Inc.
The story of "To the Moon" unfolds before players, much like a movie. While the entire game has no battle system and can be completed in a few hours, the compelling story and moving original soundtrack resonated with players worldwide. On top of receiving overwhelmingly positive ratings, "To the Moon" received multiple awards from Gamespot, Metacritic, WIRED, and more, and was nominated for "I'm Not Crying, There's Something In My Eye" in the 2016 Steam Awards.

KEY FEATURES
•	Unlocked 29 new iMessage stickers.
•	Added "Music Box" function, allowing backstage music playing& in-game music downloading(will be enabled automatically after clearing the stage).
•	Added "DIY QR code" function, allowing one-key sharing of player data for playing on different devices.
•	A unique & non-combat story-driven experience
•	Innovative mix between adventure game elements and classic RPG aesthetics
•	Acclaimed original soundtrack that closely ties to the story
•	An espresso execution with zero filler and no time drains

Languages Supported: 
* English 
* Français 
* Deutsch 
* Español (Latinoamérica) 
* Español (Europa) 
* Português 
* Polski
* lingua italiana (Italian)
* Người việt nam
* русский(Russian)
* 한국어 (Korean) 
* 简体中文 (Simplified Chinese) 
* 繁體中文 (Traditional Chinese) 
* 日本語 (Japanese)
* Türk dili(Turkish)
* Українська（Ukraine）

Facebook: /TotheMoonHD
Twitter: @TotheMoonHD
Service email: TotheMoon@xindong.com

© 2017 X.D. Network Inc. All rights reserved.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/8c/ba/e7/8cbae70f-cb96-836c-11ef-afee1d9f0995/mzl.duqjvmyj.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/0d/e0/af/0de0af90-cb76-93e7-af4a-e602fe53a13b/mzl.kcpanvyh.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/a8/b0/3f/a8b03fe9-bf55-1a2f-c386-10ff0cc7c627/mzl.ggycdnkb.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/03/c2/b2/03c2b201-1759-f62a-338f-9a0ace583983/mzl.lhameszq.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/1a/c8/d6/1ac8d620-f639-e740-db9d-2c7c9269fb60/mzl.snejulwv.jpg/406x228bb.jpg" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/48/c7/5e/48c75e27-41e0-657f-fa4d-310f414bb0cf/mzl.ukbjyhky.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/3e/bb/96/3ebb96ae-1020-2499-f408-4eee13e0b753/mzl.fefblsaa.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/a4/7c/a3/a47ca3ee-86e8-e9a2-cd46-6a14ffd1335c/mzl.elnaumho.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/a7/ac/aa/a7acaa3e-34b8-df7f-bc02-c16f32d57f61/mzl.tcljipwn.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/aa/4d/b2/aa4db242-5627-7455-6895-efbc61ce2f54/mzl.zkmbxdnw.png/552x414bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ICEY]]></title>
        <id>ICEY-1758755962690</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/icey/id1271620263?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T23:19:22.690Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺129,99 → ₺99,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/icey/id1271620263?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple125/v4/42/e4/0b/42e40bed-ba27-1450-9463-da43e44010d3/AppIcon-1x_U007emarketing-0-9-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺129,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺99,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  ICEY is a 2D side-scrolling action game. As you follow the narrator's omnipresent voice, you will see through ICEY's eyes and learn the truth about her world. 

“Alright, you caught me! This ISN'T really just a simple 2D action game, and you WON'T be seeing through ICEY's eyes... NOR will you learn the truth about her world." says the narrator. 

“ICEY is a Meta game in disguise. The narrator will constantly urge you in one direction, but you must ask, "Why? Why am I following his directions? Why can't I learn the truth about this world and ICEY's purpose here?" Fight against his tyranny, and uncover what's really going on for yourself!

In fact, you can become ICEY, and let loose the shackles of your own identity. You are ICEY, and ICEY is you... if you want it that way. Feel free to keep hold of your own self, if you wish. 

Now Is the Time For You to Discover the Truth.

[FEATURES]

Fast-paced Combat: 
Crush enemies in the palm of your hand. 
Attack! Dodge! Counterattack! Do not hesitate. 
This is the only way to survive! 

Incredible Combos: 
With simple controls, amazing combos are easy to unleash, even for beginners. 
Every skill is special in its own way. Master your favorites and create your own fighting style!

Massive Cyborg Bosses: 
Can you withstand the onslaught of attacks from terrifying cyborg bosses? 
Every boss unleashes flurries of different attacks. It's up to you to find their weak spots and tear them apart!

[Awards]
-Nominated, Tokyo Game Show 2016 DENGEKI PlayStation Best Indie Game
-Official Selection, 2016 Gamescom Indie Arena Booth 
-Most Promising Game 2nd Prize, Taipei Game Show 2016 
-Official Selection, Casual Connect Asia 2016 
-Official Selection, IGF China 2015 
-Best Technology Award, Indieplay 2015

Operating system 
iOS: version 8.0 or higher 

Recommended configuration 
RAM: 2 GB or more 
Storage: 1.2 GB (iOS) 

Tips 
- As gameplay smoothness and reliability are affected by screen resolution and the number of applications running in the background, you can adjust the image quality option to achieve balance between image, smoothness and power consumption. 

- Added MFi controller support

Languages Supported:
*English
*Francais
*Español
*简体中文 (Simplified Chinese)
*繁体中文 (Traditional Chinese)

Facebook: /ICEYtheGame
Twitter:@ICEYtheGame
Service Email: ICEY@xindong.com
2017 X.D. Network Inc. All rights reserved.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/80/31/4d/80314d42-4928-285e-ff1e-ae1ed0594fe5/mzl.paznipql.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/6b/e1/ad/6be1ad4c-c98e-9ff0-c05e-442317676aa1/mzl.ixidjdpc.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/20/bf/ec/20bfec09-f888-df7e-cb69-3e2b38d93039/mzl.qwspudpw.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/31/1e/1b/311e1b7f-65f5-6868-3533-cd7a0f937706/mzl.qxndgpfo.png/406x228bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/ce/f3/05/cef305b2-337e-46b8-4bb9-faba8a466ae7/mzl.ugthspkk.png/406x228bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/73/0e/2b/730e2b72-7942-0a0a-d991-7860268f517f/mzl.jvnwrskb.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/71/0b/42/710b42d7-f75b-d88d-5f3a-40d305126d19/mzl.qhvrhsiw.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/85/5e/92/855e9240-0e07-b317-a4ab-d649762b22f9/mzl.evnuizwl.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/70/12/d3/7012d3b7-87cb-8022-3b2c-84b36e1e43e1/mzl.rnckkema.jpg/552x414bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>