<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-10-15T16:28:22.496Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-10-15T16:28:22.497Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoneyTrack: Expense & Budget]]></title>
        <id>MoneyTrack: Expense &amp; Budget-1760545529866</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/moneytrack-expense-budget/id1473785373?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-10-15T16:25:29.866Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lifetime: ₺899,99 → ₺800,00]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/moneytrack-expense-budget/id1473785373?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/36/1b/ca/361bca41-6f29-1825-6f28-25677ba98031/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Lifetime：</strong><span>₺899,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺800,00</strong>
</b>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  MoneyTrack - Streamlined Personal Finance Tracker

Track every penny, master your financial freedom. A pure expense tracking app with no ads, no splash screens, and no investment promotions.

■ CORE FEATURES
• Auto-Tracking: Deep integration with Shortcuts allows automatic expense recording triggered by your transactions
• Comprehensive Entries: Support for income, expenses, reimbursements, transfers, credit card payments, installments, and debt management
• Insightful Analytics: Visualize spending patterns with pie charts, bar graphs and trend lines to quickly identify financial issues
• Precise Budgeting: Set annual/monthly budgets for total spending and categories with dynamic daily budget adjustments

■ COMPLETE ASSET MANAGEMENT
• Unified management of multiple account types (cash, bank cards, credit cards, store cards)
• Balance sheet and asset curve for real-time financial status tracking
• Credit card management system (payment reminders, limit management, interest-free period calculation)
• Multi-currency asset recording with support for all major currency exchange rates

■ THOUGHTFUL FUNCTIONS
• Multiple Ledgers: Flexibly separate different financial records
• Shared Accounting: Invite family and friends to maintain transparent shared finances
• Cloud Backup: Free data synchronization across devices with secure protection
• Flexible Import/Export: Support for importing data from multiple platforms and exporting in Excel format
• Recurring Entries: Customisable automatic entry tasks that generate transactions on schedule
• Installment Tracking: Easily monitor payment schedules and receive timely reminders
• Sub-Categories: Unlimited categorisation options to meet personalised needs

■ CROSS-PLATFORM EXPERIENCE
Synchronise across iPhone, iPad and PC with real-time updates, recording every expenditure wherever you are.

■ FOCUSED ON FINANCE MANAGEMENT
We do one thing only — help you better manage your personal finances. No investment promotions, no community distractions, just a pure and efficient expense tracking experience.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/70/a1/d2/70a1d289-5510-c521-b71a-1e2bd2f1f5d0/4c08a5c5-ee61-4ede-a5e3-f847aae27d3b_AppStore_U4e3b_U9875-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/a7/48/8f/a7488f10-f2d9-e187-8f74-1c211dc072eb/94a1d58a-a1ec-4f1b-9431-5b1a747e0f26_AppStore_U591c_U95f4-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/52/f5/e3/52f5e31c-7fd2-b520-e4a7-1d41e346f581/d9e33f86-70b8-499d-a193-2a83e4a7b7fd_AppStore_U7edf_U8ba1-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/ff/cd/f2/ffcdf22f-68fb-f162-a19d-770f0175df37/087f4064-82ea-4f94-b079-ff7fc0cbdd09_AppStore_U9884_U7b97-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/1d/a8/e4/1da8e450-6baf-5a3d-b710-39db4470c7ab/75ec52ca-db89-40cb-9d92-31433b7bc3c6_AppStore_U4e3b_U9875-_U7ad6_U5c4f.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>