<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/tr.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（TR）</title>
    <updated>2025-08-12T23:25:18.587Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:99063474310237184) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:99063474310237184+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T23:25:18.587Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BreatheIn: Calm Breathing]]></title>
        <id>BreatheIn: Calm Breathing-1755040940735</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/breathein-calm-breathing/id1481100296?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T23:22:20.735Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺99,99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/breathein-calm-breathing/id1481100296?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/fa/17/46/fa174617-2bb7-620c-12e2-044b8aa082d0/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007epad-0-85-220-0.jpeg/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺99,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Feeling overwhelmed by the chaos of life? Find your peace and vitality with BreatheIn, the app that helps you unlock the power of mindful breathing.

Rediscover Calm and Energy

Deep, mindful breathing is the key to a calm mind and a vibrant body. With BreatheIn, immerse yourself in guided exercises that harmonize your body and mind, leading to true balance and renewal.

Expertly Curated Practices

We've handpicked and tested each exercise to ensure you get the best. Start your journey toward a healthier, more fulfilled life today!

Seamless Apple Health Integration

Track your progress effortlessly—BreatheIn automatically syncs with Apple Health, making it easy to monitor your wellness journey.

Explore a Range of Techniques

- Square Breathing (4-4-4-4): Regain control and calm your mind.
- Relax Breathing (4-7-8): Beat anxiety and fall asleep faster.
- Bee Breathing: Soothe your mind with this relaxing technique.
- Coherent Breathing: Improve your well-being through HRV enhancement.
- Transform Your Life, One Breath at a Time

Conquer stress, boost your resilience, and rediscover balance with every breath. Download BreatheIn now and take the first step toward a more vibrant, peaceful you!
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/22/c3/01/22c30108-74a7-8d0e-4c47-9575180917f6/49c2a0f2-4368-431d-93e6-e5e7b7920078_Simulator_Screen_Shot_-_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2021-09-29_at_14.34.18.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/27/6c/f0/276cf030-d97a-2bd6-3eb8-afda930b7973/58b54ad9-5470-4977-a6ab-dd6cfce8c87b_Simulator_Screen_Shot_-_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2021-09-29_at_14.34.15.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource221/v4/02/f3/cb/02f3cbf7-6748-8e26-4c36-791525411b0f/4000a986-5670-4d10-8fe0-410a86c0c568_Simulator_Screen_Shot_-_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2021-09-29_at_14.34.13.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/29/24/4c/29244c11-c770-4285-3170-4b68845575a7/e020205e-e234-4d64-8020-04c53a71bcb2_Simulator_Screen_Shot_-_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2021-09-29_at_14.34.10.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource211/v4/e4/7e/f8/e47ef829-d42c-8980-8a97-a0cea1a5c4b3/237762f3-3dd5-42af-af62-ed187e9b8cee_Simulator_Screen_Shot_-_iPhone_8_Plus_-_2021-09-29_at_14.34.07.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planit Pro: Photo Planner]]></title>
        <id>Planit Pro: Photo Planner-1755040940735</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/planit-pro-photo-planner/id898876435?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-08-12T23:22:20.735Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: ₺449,99 → ₺229,99]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/tr/app/planit-pro-photo-planner/id898876435?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/87/4e/1c/874e1cef-c4e1-2ba8-5621-ea045e8d877d/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>₺449,99</span> → <b>
  <strong>₺229,99</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Please email info@planitphoto.com for bug reports or feature requests. Please also remember to visit https://youtube.com/playlist?list=PLTmlTTxPbBbcn1Fd1NRWTOczTY1RYEug4 for more video tutorials. Each video only lasts a few minutes but you will surely learn a lot from them. You can also reach us through Instagram. Links are under the menu inside the app.

This is a special call to landscape photographers, travel photographers, nature photographers, and those who are interested in night photography, city photography, time-lapse, star-trails, milky way or astrophotography: look no more, this is the ultimate app for you - the Planit Pro. It only costs you a cup of Frappuccino but will save you tons of time and effort and a lot of gas money. Most importantly, it will make you enjoy landscape photography even more.

Ansel Adams dedicates the beginning of his first book "Taos Pueblo" to visualization. He introduced the idea of "previsualization", which involved the photographer imagining what he wanted his final print to look like before he even took the photo. Of course, there are many great photos that were taken impromptu. However, for landscape photographers, being able to previsualize the scene before going there will greatly reduce the chance of being caught unprepared and will greatly increase the chance of getting better photos.

Photographers use various tools to help them pre-visualizing the scene. Nowadays, many of those tools are phone apps. Planit Pro is an all-in-one solution that is designed to leverage the map and simulated viewfinder technologies to provide the necessary tools for photographers to pre-visualize the scene in combination with the ground subjects and the celestial objects such as the Sun, the Moon, Stars, Star-trails and Milky Way.

In the Planit Pro app, we packed it with features - from location scouting such as GPS coordinates, elevations, distance, elevation gain, clear view, focal length, depth of field (DoF), hyperfocal distance, panorama, and aerial photography, to the Ephemeris features such as the sunrise, sunset, moonrise, moonset time and direction, twilight time, special hours of the day, sun/moon finder, major stars, constellations, nebulae azimuth and elevation angle, star trail planning, time-lapse calculation and simulation, sequence calculation and simulation, milky way searching, solar eclipse and lunar eclipse, exposure/ND filter calculator, light meter, rainbow position prediction, tide height, and tide search, etc. All the information is either represented on the map as an overlay or visually presented in simulated viewfinders (VR, AR, picture, or street view), just like you look through your camera's viewfinder. Whatever you want for your landscape photography, it is there in the Planit Pro.

Landscape photography is an adventure in the natural world. We understand that sometimes there won't be any network connection when you are out exploring. Planit Pro was designed for having it in mind. If you preload the offline elevation files and the offline mbtiles maps, you can use the app fully offline without the need for network connections.

License agreement at https://www.apple.com/legal/internet-services/itunes/dev/stdeula/
Privacy Policy at https://planitphoto.com/privacy.html
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/58/61/5e/58615e10-e036-67be-8ec0-e6dc47bc9c9b/0c7d17f8-1f8a-4ac3-825b-6ba48a2bc6fa_Final-jingmao-en.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/64/0a/ee/640aee12-c6af-7cde-c73e-dc97ef7886f8/c38dc2ae-c8c6-447d-81ce-69ed6d0fcba9_Final-mission_peak-en.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/d6/55/04/d65504fe-7ee2-66d4-98c7-a7df11678254/b4b3472f-a8af-4324-9584-5da04011a4aa_Final-travel-en.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/1c/e2/a5/1ce2a500-aa26-110a-626c-a4ffdb1d34a8/ea005c69-010c-4b6f-8d58-778d72b76da5_Final-moon_half_dome-en.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/5f/73/f9/5f73f93d-4d35-723b-0e26-628ad29cb67b/9f390872-f2e4-4636-8abe-7ca6396e95be_Final-moonbow-en.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/0e/7d/50/0e7d50d7-28ef-cdab-2ec7-a3a17f9644cc/fed6557a-7a16-458b-8a04-284ca3332b6e_Final-sunrise-en.jpg/392x696bb.jpg" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/d8/3c/93/d83c931b-e096-a8c8-f388-af4e6bfc050a/b0369de3-6e79-42eb-baca-8ff2a3756edf_Final-sunrise-en.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/80/17/a6/8017a681-b54e-6c6d-182f-ebd745885e56/e0e4fc3f-41f8-47c3-b8f7-37f0da9bf024_Final-jingmao-en.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/a0/2d/01/a02d0129-17cd-4eb3-1152-37a895dec93b/ce39395a-710a-46c8-a0f4-cf5e59904873_Final-moon_half_dome-en.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/f3/df/89/f3df8987-b43e-3add-eeaf-0ba980c7e141/cafcd749-342d-4f10-8aaa-7579f374c076_Final-mission_peak-en.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple116/v4/7f/39/9b/7f399b1a-82c0-c04c-7608-a212c3bca318/c2287f4a-930c-4965-9c49-b2ce6fdedbf5_Final-moonbow-en.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/e6/59/d8/e659d8f9-d989-0bf3-f4c4-cdaba96d0e4a/dea007a4-83d2-4f84-a34c-6c27d9fa3e39_Final-travel-en.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>