<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-09-16T15:27:19.042Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-09-16T15:27:19.043Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoneyTrack: Expense & Budget]]></title>
        <id>MoneyTrack: Expense &amp; Budget-1758036228569</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/moneytrack-expense-budget/id1473785373?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-09-16T15:23:48.569Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lifetime: $19.99 → $19.95]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/moneytrack-expense-budget/id1473785373?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/b5/bb/c1/b5bbc1c3-f4ee-8dbd-7ec0-376ee86d4d30/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>Discount Information</h2><h3>In-App Purchases</h3><ul>
  <li>
    <strong>Lifetime：</strong><span>$19.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>$19.95</strong>
</b>
  </li>
</ul><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  MoneyTrack - Smart Personal Finance Tracker
Record every dollar, take control of your finances. A clutter-free budgeting app with zero ads, zero splash screens, and zero financial product promotions.

■ KEY FEATURES
• Auto-Tracking: Seamlessly integrates with Shortcuts for automatic expense capture triggered by your transactions
• Versatile Entries: Track income, expenses, reimbursements, transfers, credit card payments, installments, and debt management
• Powerful Analytics: Visualize spending patterns through pie charts, bar graphs and trend lines to quickly spot financial issues
• Smart Budgeting: Create annual/monthly budgets for total spending and categories with dynamic daily allowance adjustments

■ COMPREHENSIVE ASSET MANAGEMENT
• Unified dashboard for all account types (cash, checking accounts, credit cards, store cards)
• Balance sheet and net worth tracking for real-time financial status monitoring
• Credit card management system (payment alerts, limit tracking, grace period calculation)
• Multi-currency support with exchange rates for all major world currencies

■ SMART FEATURES
• Multiple Books: Easily separate personal, business, and project finances
• Collaborative Tracking: Invite family members to create transparent household finances
• Cloud Sync: Free data backup across devices with secure protection
• Easy Import/Export: Support for importing from banking apps and exporting to Excel
• Recurring Transactions: Set up automatic entries that generate on schedule
• Payment Plans: Track installment payments with due date reminders
• Custom Categories: Create unlimited category levels to match your financial organization

■ MULTI-DEVICE EXPERIENCE
Sync between iPhone, iPad and PC with instant updates, keeping your financial picture complete no matter where you are.

■ FOCUSED ON FINANCIAL WELLNESS
We're dedicated to one mission — helping you achieve financial clarity. No investment pitches, no social distractions, just a clean and effective expense tracking experience.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/70/a1/d2/70a1d289-5510-c521-b71a-1e2bd2f1f5d0/4c08a5c5-ee61-4ede-a5e3-f847aae27d3b_AppStore_U4e3b_U9875-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/a7/48/8f/a7488f10-f2d9-e187-8f74-1c211dc072eb/94a1d58a-a1ec-4f1b-9431-5b1a747e0f26_AppStore_U591c_U95f4-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/52/f5/e3/52f5e31c-7fd2-b520-e4a7-1d41e346f581/d9e33f86-70b8-499d-a193-2a83e4a7b7fd_AppStore_U7edf_U8ba1-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/ff/cd/f2/ffcdf22f-68fb-f162-a19d-770f0175df37/087f4064-82ea-4f94-b079-ff7fc0cbdd09_AppStore_U9884_U7b97-_U6a2a_U5c4f.png/552x414bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple211/v4/1d/a8/e4/1da8e450-6baf-5a3d-b710-39db4470c7ab/75ec52ca-db89-40cb-9d92-31433b7bc3c6_AppStore_U4e3b_U9875-_U7ad6_U5c4f.png/576x768bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>