<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts/rss/us.xml</id>
    <title>App Store Discounts（US）</title>
    <updated>2025-06-29T03:59:15.627Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <author>
        <name>Eyelly wu</name>
        <email>eyelly.wu@gmail.com</email>
        <uri>https://github.com/eyelly-wu</uri>
    </author>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app"/>
    <subtitle>App Store Discounts - Made with love by appstore-discounts(https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts)
This message is used to verify that this feed (feedId:49753370488353792) belongs to me (userId:73658201673997312). Join me in enjoying the next generation information browser https://follow.is.
feedId:49753370488353792+userId:73658201673997312
</subtitle>
    <logo>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</logo>
    <icon>https://s3.bmp.ovh/imgs/2024/07/20/491487aec936222a.png</icon>
    <rights>Copyright (c) 2024-present Eyelly Wu</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Welcome to subscribe to App Store Discounts]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T03:59:15.628Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Thank you for subscribing to our RSS feed. We are a community-driven project dedicated to bringing the latest App Store discount information to users worldwide. Our goal is to ensure that every user can stay up-to-date with the promotional activities of their favorite apps, whether it's price reductions on the apps themselves or limited-time promotions for in-app purchases. We will cover them all for you!</p><h1>About our RSS feed</h1><ul>
  <li>Focused on delivering App Store app discount information</li><li>Whenever an app's price drops or in-app purchases go on sale, we will promptly send you a notification</li><li>Each app's discount information is presented in a separate feed</li><li>The RSS feed is completely open-source, allowing you to view, contribute, and add your favorite apps at any time</li>
</ul><h1>Find Us</h1><a href="https://github.com/eyelly-wu/appstore-discounts">App Store Discounts</a><h1>Finally</h1><p>If this project has been helpful to you, would you kindly give us a  ⭐️ </p>]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All In One Memo]]></title>
        <id>All In One Memo-1751169450562</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/all-in-one-memo/id1587301632?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T03:57:30.562Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $3.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/all-in-one-memo/id1587301632?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple122/v4/89/59/96/8959968b-9509-d517-6970-bf90d931691e/AppIcon-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-7-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$3.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Keep the words, pictures, videos, voice and positions you want to record at any time and anywhere.
And there are reminders that you can never forget.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/21/d9/b7/21d9b748-5450-6c9a-126d-c89003a8706e/f800892f-a55d-455c-ade4-0eeb7b43b15c_8plus01en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/9f/6d/bb/9f6dbb7c-38ee-d336-0747-931bdecc3bad/5e170518-34df-42b6-8675-19706b96808a_8plus02en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource116/v4/6e/4c/06/6e4c06dd-7d88-b505-c4b1-8065c89e9d44/95dcaa79-2c3f-4159-8629-21d5c4bfd435_8plus03en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/PurpleSource126/v4/e1/cc/49/e1cc49e8-6363-7f7a-d413-2b7ea3000986/be9ed823-cb8b-45ac-9c87-62c0df31eb63_8plus04en.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MovieSpirit - Movie Maker Pro]]></title>
        <id>MovieSpirit - Movie Maker Pro-1751169450562</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/moviespirit-movie-maker-pro/id1020541183?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T03:57:30.562Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $9.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/moviespirit-movie-maker-pro/id1020541183?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple126/v4/58/aa/8f/58aa8fc3-3ede-5036-6576-4f920c5138f3/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-0-0-7-0-0-sRGB-0-0-0-GLES2_U002c0-512MB-85-220-0-0.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$9.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Pay once, use forever！ You are free to use and upgrade the App in your whole life once you pay for the download once.

Do you want to share your exciting and memorable moments with someone?
Do you want to make your own movie?
Do you want to be a director, a producer, a starring actor?

In MovieSpirit, these characters can all be done by you alone!

With MovieSpirit, you can combine various media materials, such as videos, photos, music, text, recording and finger graffiti, and according to your creativity,  edit them together and add various special effects (scene switching effects, Text animation, Filter effects, video Intro, masks and so on) to create your own movie. 

Main functions:

- Crop, split, merge, cut, transform, flip and scale media clips
- Overlay multi-layers video (Picture-in-picture effect),  no limit to the number of videos or pictures
- Professional Video Ratio, Scalable Timeline (frame by frame), Unlimited Track Layers
- Add masks (Line mask, Rectangle mask, Circle mask, Text mask and Path mask options) to hide or show parts of the video
- Video matting, remove video background
- Cutout Tool (Custom Shape Tools such as Pen Tool, Lasso Tool, Smudge Tool and Text Tool can be used for image matting)
- Replace background for green/blue screen video, chroma key compositing
- up to 50 special effects options, such as Blur, Snow, Rain, Bubble, Flower, Earthquake, Mirror, Fireworks, Smoke, Vortex, flame, Starry Sky and so on
- Gradual Opaque
- Fast-Forward, Slow-Motion and reverse video (1/12 Slow to 16-fold Speed)
- Text-to-Voice function (dozens of language options)
- 360 Degrees rotating video
- Multiple Image Blending modes
- Various fonts, text templates, text colors, vertical text, emojis, shadows, text strokes, alignment etc., supports downloading new fonts from Internet or icloud 
- Built-in free music and sound effects in various styles, adding music from your computer or from iTunes, and extracting audio from videos
- Voice recording
- Draw graffiti with your finger directly on the film, variety of auxiliary drawing shape tools that can be freely selected such as straight line, curve, arrow, circle, square, triangle, star, heart, colorful text and so on
- Simple automatic tracking function
- Add movable mosaic
- Custom Background Color, such as solid color, gradient color and extract color from picture
- Dozens of Animation effects
- Adjustable Brightness, Contrast, Saturation, Exposure, White Balance, Gamma
- Create your own GIF animation
- Private Custom Intro titles (sold separately)
- Up to 80 filter effects (sketch, comics, fisheye, magnifiers, glass, background blur, rotation blur, vortex, various color filter and so on
- Up to 60 scene switching effects
- dozens of appearance shapes can be set for video/picture such as circle, heart, diamond, star, various irregular shapes and even customize unique shapes
- Can turn the video/photo into black and white, highlight the part that needs to be highlighted (Color Splash)
- Free to deform video/photo into irregular shapes
- Add motion points to video/photo/text to make them move, zoom, rotate and move together to create a variety of gorgeous effects, such as fade-in and fade-out effect and up to 100 multiple phantom effect
- Real-time preview, high resolution video output (HD)
- Import multimedia material directly from your computer via Wi-Fi: videos, photos, music and GIF animations
- Save and share videos directly to social networks such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, iCloud, WeChat, Mailbox and so on
- Helpful video tutorials


We're looking forward to any feedback and comments on MovieSpirit, and if you have any query or problem, please feel free to contact us via email verytools2006@gmail.com

We are committed to your long-term satisfaction. Thanks!
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/84/43/c6/8443c612-e66f-2cc4-5404-28496758665d/mzl.vouvntxp.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/81/a6/b9/81a6b968-db10-16b0-7122-fc4bf9a89139/mzl.irrolmav.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/5e/8d/10/5e8d104d-5b8e-8725-b913-0fec3a00d852/mzl.mhpnjkrz.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/55/22/99/552299e2-cf56-fa58-c350-3896ade7ec99/mzl.tasdcgmo.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/e5/55/80/e55580c3-ea91-dee0-2e79-6aacfa44eaa6/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><h3>iPad</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/d1/a0/dd/d1a0dd33-42a6-43d9-bd74-e4d1aaf3e727/mzl.gyaqzhtx.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/14/f8/b1/14f8b185-87f3-3d82-6b0c-e34173307848/mzl.zegpdavb.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/f2/8a/dd/f28addfb-74f5-1398-1267-8fb1cabff9e6/mzl.spbtrnit.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple113/v4/5f/3d/f1/5f3df1c1-daac-1cb8-f8c2-adf671519289/mzl.rkeuxqiq.png/576x768bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple123/v4/b8/15/b1/b815b16e-b741-2fb6-68f7-7f1a61ac89b5/pr_source.jpg/576x768bb.jpg" />]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juice Watch]]></title>
        <id>Juice Watch-1751169450562</id>
        <link href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4"/>
        <updated>2025-06-29T03:57:30.562Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Price: $6.99 → Free]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/juice-watch/id1485101937?uo=4">
  <img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple221/v4/82/e3/e8/82e3e850-3063-3dd6-dc77-d69dfb3ab5b4/AppIcon-0-0-1x_U007emarketing-0-8-0-85-220.png/60x60bb.jpg" />
</a><h2>
  Discount Information（Price：<span>$6.99</span> → <b>
  <strong>Free</strong>
</b>）
</h2><h2>Application Description</h2><p>
  Monitor your iPhone battery level from your wrist.

Juice Watch is a simple app designed to do two things well:

• Show the battery level of the paired iPhone in a complication on Apple Watch

• Deliver a notification on your iPhone when your Apple Watch is charging and gets above 90% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%)

Just glance at your wrist to monitor the charge of your iPhone throughout the day. Or, keep tabs on the battery level of your iPhone while it is plugged in and charging in another room.

You can see both your iPhone and Apple Watch battery levels on the same complication.

You can also get a notification on your Apple Watch when the paired iPhone is charging and reaches at least 80% (or whatever level you choose, from 50% to 100%).

You can set up low battery notifications, to get notifications when your Apple Watch or iPhone battery is low.

Juice Watch is available for a wide variety of complications, so you can use it on your favorite watch faces.

You can also use this app to check your Apple Watch battery level from your paired iPhone. This can be useful while your Apple Watch is charging somewhere else.

Keep in mind that the iPhone battery level shown on Apple Watch is not real-time. It is refreshed periodically, about every 5–60 minutes. The Apple Watch battery level shown on the paired iPhone refreshes at approximately the same rate.

As of iOS 17 and watchOS 10, Juice Watch reports battery levels rounded to the nearest 5% since that's now the granularity that Apple makes available to apps.
</p><h2>Application Screenshot</h2><h3>iPhone</h3><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/e7/79/05/e77905fd-8531-93f9-7e63-b31ba9d738fd/85dc5c23-12a5-430e-be68-dbbb2066cdfa_5.5_inch_-_1_-_en.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/f6/e1/e5/f6e1e581-ac55-46a4-6a3d-eeabe3789c9f/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" /><img src="https://is1-ssl.mzstatic.com/image/thumb/Purple115/v4/a2/b1/d9/a2b1d958-8649-bd40-7c70-9de4cc49a09a/pr_source.png/392x696bb.png" />]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>